Dattatray V. Bhanuse

9579764464

bhanuse.dattatray7@gmail.com

Plot No.38, Samruddhi Park, Near Kohinoor Lawns, Varud Kaji (Shendra MIDC), Aurangabad - 431201 www.linkedin.com/in/dattatray-bhanuse-82b222268/

https://github.com/BhanuseDattatray

Professional Summary

Seeking a beginner role to enhance and explore my technical knowledge gained at First bit Solutions and Indo German Too Room Aurangabad. 6 Years of Product Design Experience. I won the Entrepreneurship Development Program with First Prize challenge held at the campus and also received best kaizen implementation to automate quality inspection of ISRO parts.

Educational Background

2011-2015 Advance Diploma in Tool and Die Making

Indo German Tool Room, Aurangabad

Autonomous University

72.46

2010-2011 SSC

Vinayak Rao Patil Mahavidyala, Aurangabad

Maharashtra State Board

77%

Work Experience

Aug 2015 – Aug 2017 Design Engineer

Larsen & Toubro, Vadodara, Gujrat

Responsible for Design discussion with customer to final component

proving which includes Design.

Nov 2017 – June 2018 Junior Design Engineer

Rayon Illuminations and Energy Solutions, Aurangabad

The core responsibilities I have handled product designs and production

related fixture design.

Nov 2019 – Dec 2022 Design Engineer

Kineta Appliances and Technologies, Aurangabad

The core responsibilities I have handled product design and process.

Certification(s) Completed / Ongoing under FirstBit Solutions

Full Stack Diploma in Python Ongoing (Will be completed by July 2022)

Technical Skills

Core Technologies Core Python

Web Technologies HTML, CSS, Java Script, Bootstrap, jQuery

Database MySQL

Frameworks Flask, Django

GUI Tkinter

Data Analysis NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib

Tools Visual Studio Code

Academic Projects

1. FirstBit Solutions Project

Project Title Library Management System

Technologies Used Core Python, MySQL, Flask, File Handling

Description Library Management system is designed for managing and storing all the

data of available books in library database. It involves login of student and librarian. Library management system help in maintaining a count of books

of different categories available at library.

2. Final Year Project

Project Title Clutch Handle Pressure Die Casting Die

Technologies Used SolidWorks, NX-8, Catia, CAM

Description Clutch handle pressure casting die is designed in Catia and solidworks

software which is very rich in feature to design and also for computer aided

machining. Die casting dies are machined in 3-axis machine to avoid collision

of tools during machining fine curve of final finishing.

Awards / Achievements / Extra Curricular Activities

 Won 1st Prize in Entrepreneurship development program conducted by Indo German Tool Room, Aurangabad

Personal Information

Gender Male

Date of Birth 7 July, 1995

Hobbies Cooking

Languages Known English, Hindi, Marathi